Thank you for watching!
If I had a daughter like that, I would cry!
We are now into the second half and the last half of the show!
Here is the third event!
Infinite Jump Showdown
Well, Mr. Oshima!
What do you think will be the key to victory?
Well, I think we will do it together.
It's all about the number of times you jump.
You have to jump as hard as you can without giving up.
I hope you can jump as many as 10 times to the limit.
Are you good at jumping?
I think I am good at jumping.
I'll do my best. Trust my feet.
I'm sure I'll be fine.
I just have to make up for it here.
I'm just trying to get to the top.
I want to jump 150 times.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best to make a comeback.
Speaking of jumping, I'm Mizuki Oshita.
I don't have anything to put pressure on you.
She always jumps so high that she never comes back.
It's so high.
So high.
I'd like her to fly away safely.
I really do.
It's not that bad.
You have to fly.
If you don't fly well, you may get caught in the air, even if you think you're flying well.
But sometimes you get caught in the air.
First of all
The blue sky I wanted to see.
Riko Iwamoto
She is currently in second place overall!
And, for your information, Positive Girl Move, Hinano Himeno!
Go for it!
What do you think, Iwamoto-san? What is your enthusiasm?
Well, I'm going to jump infinitely, so I'm going to jump to my death!
To the death!
Yes, I'll do my best!
Please do your best!
Mr. Iwamoto, how many times would you like to call?
I'd like to jump to my goal!
About 100 times.
I hope to exceed 100 times.
Over 100!
Yes, sir.
I think I have a lot of patience.
I feel like I have the guts to do it.
I'm 148 centimeters tall.
And this hole is about a third of my body.
That's high.
I'm really nervous.
I think this is a good start for me.
I'm going to do my best.
Good luck!
Let's go!
The bar is so high.
Third place is possible.
And there's a chance of bon-miss.
It's a bit of a stretch, but strong doesn't always win.
Okay, are you two ready?
Let's go!
Get ready for the infinite jump showdown!
They're going high, and they're going fast, too.
Let's count the number of jumps together.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen.
Let's increase the count.
Twenty. Twenty-one. Twenty-two.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
Chinese chiunyi (Chinese chiropractor)
Landing firmly on both feet
Iwamoto is slightly aided
Do you have to stop like that?
HIMENO-chan.
You're coming pretty hard.
HIMENO...
HIMENO, in the 140s.
She's got her legs bent tight.
Thirty-nine.
40 coming.
Yamamoto's expression is changing a little
Oh, no... oh, no...
His legs should still be light.
Can he still do it? !
Forty-five.
Fifty.
Fifty-three.
Fifty-four.
Fifty-five.
HIMENO has the same style from the beginning with both legs bent
Yamamoto's legs are getting a little heavy.
Aaaatto HIMENO
Ahhhh, HIMENO
HIMENO around 60
HimenoStill, he did his best.
And Yamamoto3 strokes are coming in handy
He was up to 70.
Come on, Yamamoto, do your best!
Now in 2nd place overall
Seventy-five.
Seventy-seven.
Seventy-eight.
Coming up to 80.
80, 82, 83,
Come on, let's cheer for Iwamoto-san.
85, 86, 87, 88, 89,
90, 90, go for it!
90, go for it! Go, go, go!
90, go for it! Come on!
At the beginning, you can never stop.
It's tough because there is no upper limit.
It's my standard.
Now the goal of 100 times is approaching.
94, 95, 96,
I keep flying.
91, 98, 99,
100 is done.
100, 1, 100, 2,
Come on! Come on!
Let's still go!
109, two,
One hundred,
109,
It ends up just barely a foot high, but...
I manage to get around it.
100 up.
Eight.
109.
Coming up to 128, 129, 120
121, 122, 123, 124, 125, 6, 27, 128, 129, 130.
I got stuck on 130, so probably 129 times.
Iwamoto Riko Great record!
Nakajima
130, 135, 136, 137, 138, 139, 130
149 times
149 times.
Once stronger
One time.
Just a normal deep breath.
Deep breath.
Breathe slowly. Just slowly.
Breathe slowly. Breathe slowly.
If I hired a girl like this, I'd cry.
It's already epic.
Enjoy it, enjoy it, enjoy it.
I'm already crying I'm so moved
I'm crying until I break down
Don't listen to me for a second.
I'm gonna cry.
But you're crying because you came in last?
Manager, are you crying because you're in last place?
Manager, I'm not crying.
Good bye,
Thank you for your hard work.
Excuse me.
Just a little crackle.
Why was it me?
It's over now.
Next, we have the second group of the infinite jump showdown. The self-proclaimed number one skateboarding idol in Japan.
NGT48 Seiji Reina!
Go for it! Get in!
Kanami Tsujino, the 5th anniversary mental super-strong, super-triggering publicity department.
What do you think, Ms. Tsujino? Please tell us your enthusiasm!
Yes, I'm going to do it again.
I haven't shown my cool side yet.
I'm going to do my best to make it over 100 times.
I will do my best, believing in my own limits and everyone else's feelings.
Thank you for your support.
I'm getting nervous too.
I'm not a demon at all!
Let's go!
NGT48 with Sage Lena
And Kanami Tsujino from the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department.
And now, for the second round of the infinite jump showdown.
All right, let's get started.
One, two, three, four, five.
Okay, that's good. That's a good height.
Seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen.
We're up to 20.
Sage radar is the Corona Disaster.
It builds up over an hour of strength training.
I do my daily strength training.
I've been told that he's been beaten to a pulp.
He was temporarily looking forward to Sasaki
and at the time, he was still in his prime
Makoto Nagano said that he was rooting for Sasaki
and was cheering him on.
I'm up to the 40th!
YANJI
Tsujino Tsujino of the super 6,000 years, who is not the most adorable of Kananes.
Her specialties are mechanical gymnastics, wonders, backflips, and inverted middle.
With contributions to the Chinese era of world gymnastics.
And here's Seiji.
Oh, yeah.
For his contribution to the Chinese era of World Gymnastics.
And here's Sage.
Unfortunately, he was disqualified.
I was just before 60.
Until the sword boss and the impact
In a manner of speaking, we've made progress
I'm up to 60
61.
And then 60...
I hit it.
Just after 60...
Tsujino got hit!
Nice fight, both of you!
Sixty tons is a lot!
Thank you for your hard work!
The higher we went, the higher it went, just like Huchunvala's legs were heavy...
It was pretty tough.
But we did the best we could.
Thank you for your hard work, Mr. Chairman.
Thank you for your hard work.
I wanted to go to 400.
Oh, yeah.
I really had time to spare.
Oh, no, no, no.
I really could have afforded it.
First of all...
Not Equal Me
Mirei Suganami
AKB48
Masai Mayu
There's really not a single good thing about it so far.
I'm afraid I might disappoint my fans.
I might disappoint my fans.
I'm going to do my best to win first place in this competition.
I thought it was really cool to see all of you who jumped first.
I'm going to jump as hard as I can so that I can catch up with you.
I will do my best.
I think I have guts.
I think I can handle it.
But I worked really hard on the shuttle run earlier.
I think it's a little bit on my legs.
But I'm a little worried about that.
If you do your best without any regrets, I'll be happy.
I'm satisfied.
Let's go!
Infinite jump showdown!
All right, let's go!
One, two, three.
Was that close? Just in time for Subanami?
Six. Seven.
Eight. Nine. Ten.
Subanamimiryei is down to less than 10, and it's over.
Subanamimir layup for the win.
He's got one foot in the air.
Wait a minute.
From here on out, it's a one-man battle.
Masai Mayu.
It's okay, Masai.
He said he's confident in his leaping ability. His body is soft.
Being the eldest and having the softest body
40 48
49 50
52 53
54 55
56 57 58
59 60
I've won six 63
This is where it really counts, right here.
I kept flying to the limit, as Masai says, and I'm getting a little out of breath, but I did it.
I knew it. But it starts in the 60s.
Suddenly, everyone's in the 60s.
That's why Mr. Yamamoto is in the 60's!
Thank you, sir. - You're welcome.
Thank you very much. It's tiring.
Did it hurt your legs?
They are very tired. Thank you very much.
It's all right. I'm fine. There's still a lot more to go,
Mire-chan, you still have a lot to go. Don't worry, don't worry.
I know that you don't know how fast you are at the beginning until you try it,
I'm worried about that, too, but I'm aiming for 200 times.
Can't you do that many?
Next?
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
I'll never lose in this kind of place, either.
Well, that's great, really.
Forty-five.
Forty-six.